looxy.com 2015-12-27

# Privacy Policy | Online Dating | Looxy.com

ZDates S.A. is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy carefully when using our website or services or transacting business with us. By using our website, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

This policy (together with our terms and conditions of use and any other documents referred to in it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. By signing up to our Services and by continuing usage of the Services, you agree to bind by this policy as updated from time to time.

If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please, contact us.

## 1\. LEGAL

Our Policy applies to your use of the Looxy/GetMeChat website at www.looxy.com, http://getmechat.com/ (“Looxy/GetMeChat ” or the “site” which includes the mobile apps). We suggest you read it in conjunction with our Terms and Conditions of Use (the “Terms”). When you access or use Looxy/GetMeChat , you agree to our Privacy Policy and you consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as we’ve set out in this Policy.

This policy and any dispute or claim arising out of or in connection with it or its subject matter (including non-contractual disputes or claims) shall be governed by and construed in accordance with Panama laws. In the event there is a discrepancy between this English language version and any translated copies of the Privacy Policy, the English version shall prevail.

Looxy/GetMeChat reserves the right to change our Policy at any time and without notice, so be sure to check this Policy regularly to understand how we use your information.

IF YOU DO NOT ACCEPT AND AGREE WITH OUR PRIVACY POLICY THEN YOU MUST NOT ACCESS OR USE THE SITE.

## 2\. ABOUT US

We own and/or operate a number of social, dating, lifestyle and entertainment sites (including mobile applications/apps) and Partner Sites. We refer to our sites and apps as, collectively, the “Services” within this policy. Some of our terms will make reference to our Partner Sites and any reference in this policy to “us” or “we” or “our” will include our Partner Sites.

Looxy.com/GetMeChat.com is operated by ZDates S.A., a company registered at Ricardo J. Alfaro Avenue, Century Tower Building, 905 office, Panama, Republic of Panama.

### 2.1. OUR COMPANY

ZDates is a multifunctional platform, which offers matchmaking services, based on the use of different social preferences of its international target audience of all ages, lifestyles and demographics. It covers all the major platforms, such as websites, mobile websites and apps (iOS, Android, Windows), social network apps. It is also a perfect opportunity for business promotion and advertisement. At the same time is ZDates is an open source of sale and purchase Internet traffic.

### 2.2. OUR PARTNER SITES

If you are reading this policy you are using one of our sites or apps. We have an extensive network of sites that we categorize as Social Discovery Sites, Social Network Sites, Traditional Dating Sites and Niche Sites. The full list of our network of sites you can find on our company website. We want to offer you a full range of products and services and in order to do that we will share your details across our Partner Sites (See below Creation of duplicate profiles across our Partner Sites) and we will market our different products and services to you (See below Marketing). You authorize us to reproduce and broadcast the information contained in your profile including your name, photograph, description etc. throughout all or part of our Partner Sites for the purposes of delivering the Services to you.

## 3\. YOUR RIGHTS TO ACCESS/AMEND THE DATA WE HOLD ON YOU & OPT OUT

### 3.1. Accessing the data we hold on you

If you want to know what data we hold on you, you have a legal right to obtain this information from us. You can make a Subject Access Request at any time, in writing, by following this simple process. We reserve the right to make a small charge for this service.

To make a Subject Access Request please write to us enclosing a photocopy of a photographic ID (e.g. passport or driving license) and utility bill (to provide proof of your address). This is to ensure we only send your data to you, or a third party that you expressly authorize in writing to deal with for you.

Our address for this purpose only is Legal Dept:

ZDates S.A.

Ricardo J. Alfaro Avenue,

Century Tower Building, 905 Office,

Panama,

Republic of Panama

### 3.2. Amending/correcting the data we hold on you

If you want to amend the data we hold that’s also very easy to do. We want to make sure we have everything right so please simply contact us at support@looxy.com to make any amendments to our records.

### 3.3. Changing your consent and opting out

You always can change your mind about what data you are allowing us to keep and what you don’t want us to keep. You can amend your settings through your account at any time, or contact our Support team.

We have to advise you however, that opting out of some data processing/storage will result in a loss of functionality of the sites and a reduced user experience.

## 4\. INFORMATION WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU

We may collect and process different types of information about you. Some of this data is considered to be Personal Data (that means you can be identified by it including Sensitive Personal Data) and Anonymous Data (that is data that you cannot be identified from).

### 4.1. Information we collect when you sign up to our Services

We will collect your personal details including but not limited to your real name, user name, address, telephone, email address, date of birth, race, religion, sexual orientation and any other information you submit when you create a profile and sign up to our Services.

### 4.2. Data we collect in respect of customer service and support

If you contact customer support we will keep any information you provide to us including records of correspondence. If you provide feedback to us, or take part in any customer survey, or participate in competitions we, we will keep any information you provide.

### 4.3. Data we collect/you upload from your activity across our Services:

When you use our Services to search for other users, explore our Services, or interact with other users, we will gather data related to these activities including:

Any information you populate your profile with including photographs (see also – Important Notice about how we use your photos); Any messages that you send or receive through our sites; A record of your activity including smiles, block lists and search histories for example is also stored by us; Details of any transactions that you carry out, including any information we require to provide the products or services that you sign up to; Data from your other social network accounts if they are linked to our sites (see more details below – Information we collect from other social networks you use); Your location according to the IP address assigned to your computer machine or mobile device by your Internet Service Provider, and mobile location data (see more details below – Information we collect about your location) Usage data about how you use our site, this is what we consider Anonymous Data, which we collect using Cookies (see more details below – Our Cookie Policy)

### 4.4. Information we collect from other social networks that you use

Some of our Services have the ability to link your use of the Services to other social networks you might have access to. If you have an account with another social network e.g. Facebook, you can share the data you have on our site with that network. To enhance your experience and create a personalized service we may ask you to login to your Facebook account. By doing so you grant us access to your information stored on your Facebook profile including without limitation your personal information, photographs, videos, interests and locations. When you login to the other network or install our app, we will receive the basic information from you including but not limited to your name, photos, gender, networks, user ID, friends list and any other information you make public and your email address. If you have logged into other social networks and linked them to any of our profiles you grant permission for us to post updates, including location information, on your behalf therefore please exercise caution. You can turn off location data – see below.

### 4.5. Information we collect about your location

We can collect location data from your computer and/or mobile device. When accessing the Services from a mobile device you will be given the option to allow location sharing with our application. If you do not wish to share your location data with us please turn off this feature by following your mobile device instructions to do so. We can track your IP address if you are using a computer to access the Services. If you are using a mobile device we use GPS with an accuracy range of 20 to 100 meters. Although location data is anonymous and can’t identify you, it can be shown to other users so please exercise caution if you do not wish to publicize your location. We also use your location data to research our own Services, develop new products and improve our Services, including using third parties to help us either provide the Services to you or develop new ones, and target advertising to suit your user experience. Your devices can give us lots of information about the device including the brand, model, version of operating system, installed app details, email accounts, mobile carrier and so on. We may also connect your account with location data from Foursquare and can show your Foursquare check ins on our map within some of our Services.

### 4.6. Information we collect about your Contacts

Some features of the Services allow you to share your user experience with people you know (“your Contacts”), or to invite them to join the Services. When given the option to do so you can choose to upload your Contacts information; we will request their name and email address. If you give us your password to upload these Contacts through a web based email provider we shall not store your password after you have uploaded your Contacts’ addresses. You may also choose to invite friends through your connected social networks. You assume all responsibility for ensuring that when you select a friend to be invited by email, application or SMS that the person wants to receive that invite from you.

### 4.7. Information we collect when you activate premium account

When you take advantage of Looxy’s//GetMeChat's premium features, we collect financial information necessary to process your payments as per your chosen payment method. Please note that we do not store any credit card or other payment card details. However, our payment service providers do (and are approved to do so by all applicable regulatory bodies).

## 5\. HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

We process data we collect from you for the following core purposes:

  * To administer your user account with us (including notifying you of any compatible matches, incoming site events and messages, tips, announcements, updates, special offers or services, should you consent to this);

  * To help us improve the structure, layout and usability of the Services;

  * To allow you to participate in any interactive features of the Services (including the features that require the mobile phone number);

  * To help personalize your repeat visits to and usage of the Services;

  * To notify you of any compatible matches or any matches who are near your location;

  * To provide you with information on products or services or news and offers that you request from us (see below under 'Marketing' for more information);

  * To answer any questions you may raise or respond to any comments you may send to us;

  * To notify you about changes to our service or the functionality of the Site;

  * To carry out market analysis and research;

  * To ensure that you are complying with the terms and conditions of use and to comply with our statutory and regulatory obligations.

### 5.1. Creation of duplicate profiles across our Partner Sites

When you sign up to any one of our Services we will send you an email shortly afterwards advising that we have created a duplicate profile on our Partner Sites to enhance your chance of finding a suitable match. When we email you about this you will have the option to decline this service, which costs nothing extra.

### 5.2. Important notice about how we use your photographs

As we explain in our terms and conditions, when you upload a photo to any of our Services you are allowing us to use that photo for advertising and other commercial purposes, royalty free. For full details please refer to our terms and conditions.

### 5.3. How we use your information about your Contacts

If you choose to upload your Contact’s name and email address and/or mobile number you are allowing us to send an email or social network or mobile invitation on your behalf, inviting your Contact to join the Services. We will store your Contact’s name and email address solely for the purposes of inviting them to sign up to our Services and for associating your Contact with you and other people they may know. If your Contact does not want us to store their email address which you uploaded to our Services, they can ask us to remove it by contacting us support@looxy.com. We will not store your Contacts information after invitations (up to a maximum of 3) have been sent. Your Contacts will then only receive future emails from us if they choose to accept the invitation and join our Services, or if you use any of our tools to share experiences with your Contacts and you input their email address for us to use again.

### 5.4. When we disclose your information to third parties and why

We may be required by law e.g. through potential or actual litigation, court order, public or governmental authorities, or rules and regulations within or out with your country of residence to disclose all or part of your information to third parties. We may also deem it necessary to make such a disclosure in the event of an issue of national security, law enforcement or other such similar situations as we deem necessary including, for example, allegations of alleged infringement of copyright, trade marks or other third parties’ rights by users. We share your personal information with third party service providers in order to provide the Services to you including third parties who assist us with information processing, credit and payment processing, fulfillment of your subscription order, managing and hosting data, conducting consumer research or satisfaction surveys. These disclosures relate to providing our Services, improving our Services and delivering targeted advertising to you. We do not provide your contact details to third parties for direct marketing by them to you without your express consent, which will be obtained from you at sign up process if you elect to provide this consent. As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy assets. In such transactions, the information we have collected about you will generally be one of the transferred business assets. Also in the unlikely event that our Company or our assets are purchased, your information will also be one of the transferred assets. We may share information about you with: Other companies in the same corporate group as us. A buyer or prospective buyer of our business. Our professional advisers, such as our lawyers, where it is necessary for them to advise us. Other persons if we are under a duty to disclose or share your information in order to comply with any legal obligation.

## 6\. MARKETING

### 6.1. When we market to you directly about our products and services

We may share your information with our Partner Sites to develop and deliver targeted advertising to you of our Partner Sites’ products and services, or to help us to prepare marketing reports. We may send you information about our Partner Sites’ products and services, news and offers, and selected third party products and services that we think may be of interest to you. We may do this by contacting you through your email address or mobile phone number that you have provided. Any communication received from us, as consented to by you, will clearly state that it is being sent by us. You have the option to opt-out of our marketing communications at any time (see below).

When you become a Member, you agree and consent to receive email messages from us. These emails may be transactional or relationship communications relating to the Service, such as administrative notices and service announcements or changes, or emails containing commercial offers, promotions, special offers from us or information regarding other users activity regarding your account.

### 6.2. When third parties market to you (Our “third party Partner Services”)

If you have consented to receive marketing communications from third parties during our sign up process, referred to as Partner Services, your data may be passed on to such third parties as we enter into data sharing agreements with, from time to time, for marketing and analytical reporting purposes. We cannot be held liable for the content of the third party’s communications or products/services they are promoting. If you have provided this consent, but change your mind, you can opt-out at any time (see below). Please be advised that you will also require to contact the individual third parties who have been marketing to you if you wish to stop receiving their communications directly.

### 6.3. Opting Out of Marketing

If you change your mind about the marketing consent you have granted to us, you can amend your preferences under the “Settings” section of your chosen Site, under the “Unsubscribe” section of any email or emailing us at support@looxy.com.

## 7\. WHERE WE STORE YOUR DATA

The personal data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a location outside the European Economic Area ('EEA') including but not limited to USA where we host our servers. It may also be processed by law enforcement agencies, employees and independent contractors of our Company located outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers (for example, staff who are involved in providing services that you order from us, processing your payment details or providing support services to us). By submitting your personal data to us, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

## 8\. HOW LONG WE KEEP YOUR DATA FOR

Generally speaking, we only store data for as long as it is necessary to provide products and Services to you and others, with information typically being held until you cancel your membership.

For data storage purposes however our users are considered as either being:

  * Active Users; this means you regularly log on to our Services and use the Services in any way;

  * Inactive Users: this means that you have not cancelled your account but you haven’t logged in for 6 months, or conducted any activity on our Services in that time;

  * Cancelled: this means that you have followed our cancellation process and actively cancelled your membership.

### 8.1. Active Users

If you are an Active User we will store your data until you cancel your account.

### 8.2. Inactive Users

If you are an Inactive User, you should be aware that we will continue to store your data until you cancel you account, including continue to market to you if you have consented to marketing. Just because you haven’t logged on for a few months, we hope you will return to use the Services regularly and we want your information to be there for your convenience so you should be aware that you will still appear in our search results for other users, and your profile will remain visible. The responsibility to change your preferences or cancel your account lies with you.

### 8.3. Cancelled Users

If you are a Cancelled User, we will delete all of your data 9 months after the date of cancellation. It is important that we retain your data for this short period after cancellation to ensure that we can answer any payment or other account related queries, or provide information to third parties in line with our disclosure provisions outlined in this policy e.g. assisting police investigations. Even after you remove information from your profile or delete your account, copies of that information may still be viewable and/or accessed on the Internet to the extent such information has been previously shared with others, or copied or stored by other users or to the extent such information has been shared with search engines. We cannot control this, nor do we accept any liability for this. If you have given third party applications or websites access to your personal information they may retain such information to the extent permitted under their terms of service or privacy policies.

### 8.4. Storage of activity data

Whilst we retain your Personal Data, Sensitive Personal Data and Anonymous Data as outlined at (a) to (c) above, there are some features of our Services that we store data in respect of, for different periods of time. For example, messages are only stored for 180 days, smiles, likes and other similar activities are stored for 30 days. All other profile and activity information including photographs, blocked list, search histories etc. are stored until 9 months after your account is cancelled.

## 9\. KEEPING YOUR DATA SECURE

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to the Site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorized access. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password or user ID code which enables you to access certain parts of the Site, you are responsible for keeping the password or user ID code confidential. We ask you not to share a password or user ID code with anyone.

## 10\. OUR COOKIE POLICY

We may collect information about your computer or mobile device by using Cookies. If you use our site you are consenting to the use of Cookies as explained here. Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit and provide statistical data to us, that does not identify you personally but it tell us a lot about your browsing habits to tailor your user experience to suit your needs. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the site. We use cookies to enhance our security, help us gather information during subscription and understand our web traffic trends and to share your non-personal information with carefully selected third parties for marketing purposes.

Cookies help us to improve the Services and to deliver a better and more personalized service. They enable us:

  * To estimate our audience size and usage pattern;

  * To store information about your preferences, and so allow us to customize the Services according to your individual interests;

  * To speed up your searches;

  * To recognize you when you return to any website or application;

  * To provide annoymised statistical information: Non-personal data may be gathered on our behalf using cookies, log file data, and code that is embedded on our websites by specific third party partners to help these selected third parties to deliver relevant advertisements to you.

We use this non-personal information to help improve the services we provide to you. When you visit the publicly available sections of the Services, a session ID cookie is placed on your computer that only lasts while you’re visiting. We also place persistent cookies (also known as local storage devices) on members’ computers, so that we remember them to make your login in process faster and easier.

### 10.1. Controlling and deleting cookies

You have the right to choose whether or not to accept cookies and we explain how you can exercise this right below. However, please note that if you choose to refuse cookies you may not be able to use the full functionality of our Sites and the websites of other companies. You may block cookies in several ways:

  * by using the opt-outs provided below;

  * by visiting http://www.youronlinechoices.com/; or

  * through your browser, as explained below.

You can also block cookies by changing your browser settings so that cookies from this Site cannot be placed on your computer or mobile device. In order to do this follow the instructions provided by your browser (usually located within the "Help", "Tools" or "Edit" facility). Disabling a cookie or category of cookie does not delete the cookie from your browser; you will need to do this yourself from within your browser.

Further information about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set on your device and how to manage and delete them, visit www.aboutcookies.org and www.youronlinechoices.eu.

### 10.2. What cookies are used for and why we use them on this Site

This table shows fully the cookie functions and why they are used, although our uses may change over time and it is important that you revisit this page to understand these uses:

**Cookie Functions**

| 

**Cookie Purposes**  
  
---|---  
  
Analytics and research

| 

We use the information collected by Google Analytics to compile reports and to help us improve the site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited. You can opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout#sthash.1CRxgddB.dpuf  
  
Authentication

| 

These cookies help us to identify our members so that when you’re logged in, you can enjoy all of the features without having to continually log in – our website “remembers” you and allows you full access without the need to keep entering your log in details.  
  
Security and site integrity

| 

We may use cookies and other devices, such as CAPTCHAs, to help keep the Site and our members safe and secure by protecting the Site from fraud and spam attacks to keep your data safe.  
  
Site features and services

| 

These cookies and local storage devices provide the functionality that our members enjoy, such as uploading of photographs, chats, instant messaging, your account settings etc. We also use cookies to help provide experiences, such as links to other social media sites, social plugins and video content, including making it easier for you to share content between the website with your other favorite social networks. In some cases, the site feature you choose may allow a third party to place cookies or local storage devices on your computer. The third party who places cookies on your device is responsible for how they process their data you should always read their privacy policies. Third parties who place cookies on your device when you use the Site include Twitter and Facebook whose own privacy policies apply.  
  
Performance

| 

We need to use certain cookies and local storage devices to ensure our members have the best possible experience, such assisting with your navigation of our site, ensuring pages load up quickly and respond faster to your requests for our Services.  
  
Ad Serving & Behavioral Advertising

| 

We sell space on some of our websites to advertisers. We use several services to help us and advertisers understand what adverts you might be interested in. These cookies hold information about the computer - they don't hold personal information about you (i.e. it's not linked to you as an individual). But they might hold a record of what other websites you've looked at - so we could show you a car advert if you've previously visited a motoring website.   
Advertisements on this Site and the other sites you visit are provided by other organizations. Our advertising partners will serve advertisements that they believe are most likely to be of interest to you, based on information about your visit to the Site and other websites. In order to do this, our advertising partner may need to place a cookie on your computer.   
For more information about this type of online behavioral advertising, about cookies, and about how to turn this feature off, please visit [www.youronlinechoices.eu](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/) and select your country.   
These are some examples of the services we use and how you can control those cookies. This list is not exhaustive and is subject to change. Please visit [www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/) for active cookie management on your device.   
Please note that turning off advertising cookies won't mean that you are not served any advertising merely that it will not be tailored to your interests. 

  * OpenX (advertising) Privacy policy and opt-out via [http://www.openx.com/about/privacy-policy](http://www.openx.com/about/privacy-policy)

  * VisualDNA (ad relevancy): Privacy policy at [http://www.visualdna.com/cookie-policy](http://www.visualdna.com/cookie-policy) and you can opt out via [http://my.visualdna.com/permissions/](http://my.visualdna.com/permissions/)

  * Lotame (ad relevancy): Privacy policy at [http://www.lotame.com/privacy](http://www.lotame.com/privacy) and opt out via [http://www.lotame.com/opt-out-preference-manager](http://www.lotame.com/opt-out-preference-manager)

  * Doubleclick (advertising): Privacy policy at [http://www.google.com/doubleclick/privacy/](http://www.google.com/doubleclick/privacy/) and opt out via [http://www.youronlinechoices.com/](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/)

  * eXelate (ad relevancy): Privacy policy and opt out via [http://exelate.com/consumer-opt-out/](http://exelate.com/consumer-opt-out/)

  * Google Adsense (ad partner). Privacy policy at [https://support.google.com/adsense/bin/answer.py?hl=en-GB&utm_medium=link&gsessionid=DyXLmLB1J1MxXckh6tX6AQ&utm_campaign=ww-ww-et-asfe_&utm_source=aso&answer=48182](https://support.google.com/adsense/bin/answer.py?hl=en-GB&utm_medium=link&gsessionid=DyXLmLB1J1MxXckh6tX6AQ&utm_campaign=ww-ww-et-asfe_&utm_source=aso&answer=48182) and opt-out via [https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/).

### 10.3. Web Beacons

Web beacons (also known as clear gifs, pixel tags or web bugs) are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of web users or to access cookies. Unlike cookies, which are stored on the user's computer hard drive, web beacons are embedded invisibly on the web pages (or in email) and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence.

Web beacons may be used to deliver or communicate with cookies, to count users who have visited certain pages and to understand usage patterns. We also may receive an anonymous identification number if you come to our site from an online advertisement displayed on a third-party website. Third parties may use anonymous information about your visits to our site and other websites in order to improve its products and services and provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

## 11\. OUR RIGHTS TO AMEND THIS POLICY

We keep our privacy policy under regular review and will post any changes to it on this page. We encourage you to regularly review our privacy policy to make sure you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we may share it with other parties. We may also contact you from time to time to advise of any changes if we feel such notification is necessary depending on the extent of the changes.

## 12\. LINKS TO OTHER THIRD PARTY WEBSITES

Our websites, apps, and promotional materials, may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our third party networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

## 13\. ADDITIONAL PRIVACY PROTECTIONS FOR CHILDREN USING THE INTERNET

We do not solicit or target persons younger than legal age for collection of information online. Our Site does not permit children under the age of 18 to become users and we do not accept any information from children. By submitting information to us you represent that you are over the age of 18. We encourage minors to seek the consent of their parents before providing any information about themselves or their households to anyone on the Internet. We encourage parents to take an active role to protect the privacy and security of their children and to prevent the inappropriate use of information about their children. We support the development of technologies that help parents to control the collection and use of personal information from children who use online services in their households.
